Finding Aid for Michigan Daily Records, 1950-2006
Bentley Historical Library
- Faculty, Staff, Administrators-Biographical Files, 5 linear feet
  - I-L
    - Kuhn, Sherman McAllister -- English (Box 15)
    - Kung, Hans -- Near Eastern Studies (Box 15)
    - Kurath, Hans -- English (Box 15)
    - Lado, Robert -- Eng. Lang. Inst (Box 15)
    - Lagler, Karl F. -- Zoology (Box 15)
    - Lahti, Aarre K. -- Design (Box 15)
    - Laing, Lionel H. -- Political Science (Box 15)
    - Lamb, Karl A. -- Political Science (Box 15)
    - LaMore, Chet H. -- Drawing, Painting (Box 15)
    - Lampe, Isadore -- Radiology (Box 15)
    - Landes, Kenneth K. -- Geology (Box 15)
    - Lane, Harlan -- Psychology (Box 15)
    - Langford, Cooper H. -- Philosophy (Box 15)
    - Langmore, John P. -- Biophysics (Box 15)
    - Lanham, Frank W. -- Education (Box 15)
    - Lapides, Jack -- Surgery (Box 15)
    - Laporte, Otto -- Physics (Box 15)
    - Larkin, Thomas J. -- Art (Box 15)
    - Larson, C. Theodore -- Architecture (Box 15)
    - Lawiewski, Robert C. -- Zoology (Box 15)
    - Latourette, Howard B. -- Radiology (Box 15)
    - Lauer, Edward W. -- Anatomy (Box 15)
    - Lawrence, Merle -- Medicine (Box 15)
    - Lay, Walter E. -- Mech. Engineering (Box 15)
    - Leabo, Dick A. -- Statistics (Box 16)
    - Leach, Kent W. -- Education (Box 16)
    - Leatherman, Roger L. -- Phoenix Project (Box 16)
    - Lee, Gilbert L. -- Controller (Box 16)
    - Legatski, Leo M. -- Civil Engineering (Box 16)
    - Lehman, John T. -- Biology (Box 16)
    - Lehmann, Charles F. -- Education (Box 16)
    - Liebee, Howard C. -- Physical Education (Box 16)
    - Leith, Emmet -- Electrical Eng (Box 16)
    - Lemler, Ford L. -- Audio Visual (Box 16)
    - Lenski, Gerhard E. -- Sociology (Box 16)
    - Leonard, Irving A. -- Spanish Amer. Lit (Box 16)
    - Leonhard, Wolfgang -- History (Box 16)
    - Leslie, Elizabeth -- Housing (Box 16)
    - Leslie, William R. -- History (Box 16)
    - LeVeque, William -- Math (Box 16)
    - Levine, Melvin -- Biological Chemistry (Box 16)
    - Levinson, Harold M. -- Economics (Box 16)
    - Levy, Stanley R. -- Literary College Admin. Asst (Box 16)
    - Lewis, James A. -- Vice President for Student Affairs (Box 16)
    - Lewis, Louis W. -- Anesthesiology (Box 16)
    - Likert, Rensis -- Social Research (Box 16)
    - Liller, William -- Astronomy (Box 16)
    - Lillya, Clifford P. -- Music (Box 16)
    - Lindstrom, Carl -- Journalism (Box 16)
    - Lippitt, Ronald -- Psychology (Box 16)
    - Liss, Leopold -- Psychiatry (Box 16)
    - Litwak, Eugene -- Social Work (Box 16)
    - Litzenberg, Karl -- English (Box 16)
    - Llewellyn, Frederick B. -- Scientific Advisor (Box 16)
    - Rostovsky, Andrei -- History (Box 16)
    - Loehr, Max -- Fine Arts (Box 16)
    - Loescher, Robert J. -- History of Art (Box 16)
    - Lohwater, Arthur J. -- Math (Box 16)
    - Long, Nicholas J. -- Psychiatry (Box 16)
    - Louis, Lawrence H. -- Biological Chemistry (Box 16)
    - Lovell, Robert G. -- Internal Medicine (Box 16)
    - Loving, Alvin D. -- Education (Box 16)
    - Lowell, John H. -- Music (Box 16)
    - Lowenthal, Lois A. -- Zoology (Box 16)
    - Lowrey, George H. -- Pediatrics (Box 16)
    - Lowry, Robert James -- Botany (Box 16)
    - Luconi, Albert -- Clarinet (Box 16)
    - Ludlow, H. Glenn -- Education (Box 16)
    - Ludwig, Elizabeth A. -- Physical Education (Box 16)
    - Lund, Donald A. -- Baseball Coach (Box 16)
    - Lyons, Chalmers J. -- Dentistry (Box 16)
    - Maassab, Hunien -- Public Health (Box 16)
    - MacCarthy, Alan W. -- Development Council (Box 16)
    - MacDonald, Donald L. -- Insurance (Box 16)
    - MacDonald, Glenn -- Student Publications (Box 16)
    - Maddy, Joseph E. -- Music (Box 16)
    - Magielski, John E. -- Medicine (Box 16)
    - Maier, Norman F. -- Psychology (Box 16)
    - Makdisi, George -- Near East Studies (Box 16)
    - Malcolmson, Reginald -- Dean of Art & Design (Box 16)
    - Malm, William P. -- Music (Box 16)
    - Malvin, Richard L. -- Physiology (Box 16)
    - Mann, Floyd C. -- Psychology (Box 16)
    - Manning, John J. -- Jr.-Sr. Counseling, Admin. Asst (Box 16)
    - Mao, James C. T. -- Finance (Box 16)
    - Marckwardt, Albert H. -- English (Box 16)
    - Marin, Axel -- Mech. Engineering (Box 16)
    - Marra, Alan A. -- Wood Technology (Box 16)
    - Marshall, Norma K. -- Asst. Dean of Nursing School (Box 16)
    - Martel, William -- Radiology (Box 16)
    - Martin, Edwin R. -- Electrical Eng (Box 16)
    - Martin, Joseph J. -- Chemical and Metallurgical Eng (Box 16)
    - Martin, Michael M. -- Organic Chemistry (Box 16)
    - Mason, Marilyn -- Organ (Box 16)
    - Mason, Merle -- Biological Chemistry (Box 16)
    - Mast, Gerald -- Arch. & Design (Box 16)
    - Mastin, Glenn G. -- Architecture (Box 16)
    - Mathews, Kenneth P. -- Internal Medicine (Box 16)
    - Mattocks, Albert M. -- Pharmacy (Box 16)
    - Maurer, Evan Maclyn -- Museum of Art (Box 16)
    - Maurer, Wesley H. -- Journalism (Box 16)
    - Mazrui, Ali -- Afro-Amer. Studies (Box 16)
    - McCain, R. Faye -- Nursing (Box 16)
    - McCarus, Ernst N. -- Near Eastern Studies (Box 16)
    - McCleary, Robert A. -- Psychology (Box 16)
    - McClure, Thomas F. -- Design (Box 16)
    - McClusky, Howard Y. -- Educational Psych (Box 16)
    - McConnell, James V. -- Psychology (Box 16)
    - McCoy, Lester -- Univ. Musical Soc (Box 16)
    - McCracken, Paul -- Business Admin (Box 16)
    - McCready, Donald W. -- Chemical Engineering (Box 16)
    - McGeoch, Glenn D. -- Music (Box 16)
    - McHargue, Daniel S. -- Political Science (Box 16)
    - McInally, William K. -- Regent (Box 16)
    - McKeachie, Wilbert H. -- Psychology (Box 16)
    - McKevitt, John -- Asst. to Vice-Pres. of Business/Finance (Box 16)
    - McLaughlin, Dean B. -- Astronomy (Box 16)
    - McMath, Robert R. -- Astronomy (Box 16)
    - McMurry, Kenneth C. -- Geography (Box 16)
    - McNamara, Leo -- Irish History (Box 16)
    - McNeil, Ella E. -- Public Health (Box 16)
    - McNeil, Elton B. -- Psychology (Box 16)
    - McNerney, Walter J. -- Hospital Admin (Box 16)
    - McVaugh, Rogers -- Botany (Box 16)
    - Medlin, William K. -- Education (Box 16)
    - Mednick, Sarnoff Andrei -- Psychology (Box 16)
    - Meier, Richard L. -- Natural Resources (Box 16)
    - Meiland, Jack -- Philosophy (Box 16)
    - Mendel, Arthur -- History (Box 16)
    - Mendenhall, George E. -- Near Eastern Studies (Box 16)
    - Menlo, Allen -- Education (Box 16)
    - Merchant, Donald J. -- Bacteriology (Box 16)
    - Merhab, William G. -- Romance Languages (Box 16)
    - Mersereau, John -- Slavic Languages (Box 16)
    - Meyer, Donald I. -- Physics (Box 16)
    - Meyer, Henry J. -- Social Work (Box 16)
    - Meyers, Muriel C. -- Internal Medicine (Box 16)
    - Milholland, John E. -- Psychology (Box 16)
    - Miller, Arthur -- Political Science (Box 16)
    - Miller, Daniel R. -- Psychology (Box 16)
    - Miller, Freeman D. -- Astronomy (Box 16)
    - Miller, James G. -- Psychiatry (Box 16)
    - Miller, Lila -- Biological Chemistry (Box 16)
    - Miller, N. Edd -- Speech (Box 16)
    - Miller, Richard D. -- Voice (Box 16)
    - Miller, Robert -- Zoology (Box 16)
    - Miller, Seward E. -- Industrial Health (Box 16)
    - Miller, Warren E. -- Political Science (Box 16)
    - Mills, William H. -- Education (Box 16)
    - Milosovich, George -- Pharmacy (Box 16)
    - Miner, Horace M. -- Sociology (Box 16)
    - Mitchell, Elmer D. -- Physical Education (Box 16)
    - Moffett, James W. -- Zoology (Box 16)
    - Moise, Edward -- Math (Box 16)
    - Moise, Edwin E. -- Math (Box 16)
    - Monsour, Sally A. -- Music Education (Box 16)
    - Moore, Arthur D. -- Electrical Eng (Box 16)
    - Moore, Earl V. -- Music (Box 16)
    - Moore, Franklin G. -- Industrial Mgmt (Box 16)
    - Moore, Thomas E. -- Biology (Box 16)
    - Moosman, Darvan A. -- Anatomy (Box 16)
    - Moravcsik, Julius M. -- Philosophy (Box 16)
    - Morgan, James N. -- Economics (Box 16)
    - Morgan, Robert O. -- Alumni Association (Box 16)
    - Morrison, Richard B. -- Aeronautical Eng (Box 16)
    - Morse, William -- Educational Psych (Box 16)
    - Rand, Morton F. -- Spanish (Box 16)
    - Moulton, Robert W. -- Psychology (Box 16)
    - Mouzon, James C. -- Electrical Eng (Box 16)
    - Muehl, John F. -- English (Box 16)
    - Mueller, Florian F. -- Music (Box 16)
    - Mueschke, Paul -- English (Box 16)
    - Mullen, Albert P. -- Art (Box 16)
    - Muller, Robert H. -- University Library (Box 16)
    - Murphy, Irene -- Regent (Box 16)
    - Murphy, Marjorie M. -- Nutrition (Box 16)
    - Murrays, N. Patrick -- English (Box 16)
    - Muschenheim, William -- Architecture (Box 16)
    - Musgrave, Richard A. -- Economics (Box 16)
    - Myers, Alison T. -- Alumnae Secretary (Box 16)
    - Myers, George E. -- Education (Box 16)
    - Myers, Philip -- Biology (Box 16)
    - Nace, George W. -- Biology (Box 16)
    - Naghdi, Paul M. -- Engineering Mech (Box 16)
    - Nagy, Andrew -- Atmospheric and oceanic sciences (Box 16)
    - Needler, Martin C. -- Political Science (Box 16)
    - Neel, James V. -- Genetics (Box 16)
    - Nelson, Geneva C. -- Music Education (Box 16)
    - Nelson, J. Raleigh -- English, Int'l Ctr (Box 16)
    - Nelson, Jack A. -- Asst. Football Coach (Box 16)
    - Nelson, Norman E. -- English (Box 16)
    - Nelson, Roger B. -- University Hospital (Box 16)
    - Nelson, Roy -- French (Box 16)
    - Nelson, Wilbur C. -- Aeronautical Eng (Box 16)
    - Nesbit, Reed M. -- Surgery (Box 16)
    - Newcomb, Theodore M. -- Psychology, Sociology (Box 16)
    - Newell, Barbara -- Acting Vice Pres. for Student Affairs (Box 16)
    - Niehuss, Marvin L. -- Vice President and Dean of -- Faculties (Box 16)
    - Niess, Robert J. -- French (Box 16)
    - Noehren, Robert -- Organ (Box 16)
    - Noffsinger, Mark G. -- Coordinator of Counseling (Box 16)
    - Nooden, Larry D. -- Botany (Box 16)
    - Nordmeyer, Henry W. -- German (Box 16)
    - Norman, A. Geoffrey -- Vice President for Research (Box 16)
    - Norman, Warren T. -- Psychology (Box 16)
    - Northcutt, R. Glenn -- Zoology (Box 16)
    - Norton, Hugh Z. -- Speech (Box 16)
    - Nungester, Walter J. -- Bacteriology (Box 16)
    - Nussbaum, Ronald -- Zoology (Box 16)
    - Oakley, Bruce -- Biology (Box 16)
    - Oberdick, Willard A. -- Architecture (Box 16)
    - O'Connor, Basil -- Honorary Degree (Box 16)
    - O'Dell, Frederick C. -- Architecture (Box 16)
    - Ogden, Henry V. S. -- English (Box 16)
    - Ohlgren, Harold A. -- Chemical Engineering (Box 16)
    - Okey, Loren L. -- Speech (Box 16)
    - Oksenberg, Michel -- Political Science (Box 16)
    - Oliver, William J. -- Pediatrics (Box 16)
    - Olson, Willard C. -- Education (Box 16)
    - O'Neill, James C. -- French (Box 16)
    - Oosterbaan, Bennie G. -- Football Coach (Box 16)
    - Oppenheim, S. Chesterfield -- Law (Box 16)
    - Ormondroyd, Jesse -- Engineering Mech (Box 16)
    - O'Roke, Earl -- Zoology (Box 16)
    - Ostrander, Floyd D. -- Dentistry (Box 16)
    - Overberger, Charles -- Vice President for Research (Box 16)
    - Owen, Marian A. -- Piano (Box 16)
  - P-S
    - Page, Edward L. -- Industrial Eng (Box 16)
    - Palazzola, Guy J. -- Art (Box 16)
    - Palmer, George E. -- Law (Box 16)
    - Palmer, William B. -- Economics (Box 16)
    - Paper, Herbert H. -- Near Eastern Studies (Box 16)
    - Park, Richard L. -- Political Science (Box 16)
    - Parks, David G. -- Asst. to Vice Pres. for Univ. Relations (Box 16)
    - Parker, Ivan W. -- Asst. Dean of Men (Box 16)
    - Parkinson, William C. -- Physics (Box 16)
    - Parravano, Giuseppe -- Chemical Engineering (Box 16)
    - Parry, Robert W. -- Chemistry (Box 16)
    - Parsons, Thomas S. -- Education (Box 16)
    - Patno, Mary Ellen -- Public Health Stats (Box 16)
    - Paton, William Andrew Sr. -- Economics, Acctg (Box 16)
    - Paton, William A., Jr. -- Business Admin., Flint College (Box 16)
    - Paul, A. G. -- Pharmacy (Box 16)
    - Payne, Robert B. -- Zoology (Box 16)
    - Peak, Helen -- Psychology (Box 16)
    - Pealy, Robert H. -- Public Admin (Box 16)
    - Pearce, Jack R. -- Law (Box 16)
    - Pearson, Ross N. -- Geography (Box 16)
    - Pease, Esther E. -- Physical Education (Box 16)
    - Peckman, Howard H. -- Clements Library (Box 16)
    - Peek, George A., Jr. -- Political Science (Box 16)
    - Peery, David J. -- Aeronautical Eng (Box 16)
    - Pelz, Donald C. -- Survey Research Ctr (Box 16)
    - Penix, Findlay C. -- Education (Box 16)
    - Penzl, Herbert -- German (Box 16)
    - Perigo, William J. -- Physical Education (Box 16)
    - Perkins, John A. -- Political Science (Box 16)
    - Perrow, Charles -- Sociology (Box 16)
    - Peter, Hollis W. -- Fdn. for Research on Human Behavior (Box 16)
    - Peterson, Gordon E. -- Speech (Box 16)
    - Peterson, George Shorey -- Economics (Box 16)
    - Petoskey, E. Jack -- Registration (Box 16)
    - Peyton, Floyd A. -- Dentistry (Box 16)
    - Phelps, Dudley M. -- Marketing (Box 16)
    - Phillips, George L. -- Pharmacy (Box 16)
    - Phillips, Glen D. -- Univ. Broadcasting (Box 16)
    - Pidd, Robert W. -- Physics (Box 16)
    - Pierce, Roy -- Political Science (Box 16)
    - Pierce, William J. -- Law (Box 16)
    - Pierpont, Wilbur K. -- Vice President for Business and Finance (Box 16)
    - Pike, Kenneth L. -- Linguistics (Box 16)
    - Pilcher, Clayton J. -- Finance (Box 16)
    - Pinkus, Helen S. -- Social Work (Box 16)
    - Piper, Adrian M. Smith -- Philosophy (Box 16)
    - Place, Irene -- Office Management (Box 16)
    - Plumer, James M. -- Fine Arts (Box 16)
    - Poehle, Herbert F. -- Engineering Research Institute (Box 16)
    - Polasky, Alan N. -- Law (Box 16)
    - Pollack, Henry -- Geology (Box 16)
    - Pollard, Herman Marvin -- Internal Medicine (Box 16)
    - Pollmar, Carl H. -- Engineering Research Institute (Box 16)
    - Porter, Richard J. -- Protozoology (Box 16)
    - Porter, Richmond C. -- Mech. Engineering (Box 16)
    - Porter, William -- Journalism (Box 16)
    - Porterfield, John D. -- Public Health (Box 16)
    - Pott, Clarence K. -- German (Box 16)
    - Potts, Philip O. -- Engineering Drawing (Box 16)
    - Power, Eugene B. -- Regent (Box 16)
    - Power, Sarah Goddard -- Regent (Box 16)
    - Prendergast, James D. -- Drawing, Painting (Box 16)
    - Prentice, John T., Jr. -- Admissions (Box 16)
    - Preston, Stephen B. -- Wood Technology (Box 16)
    - Preston, William S. -- Bacteriology (Box 16)
    - Price, Percival -- Campanology (Box 16)
    - Pringle, John R. -- Cellular & Molecular Biology (Box 16)
    - Proffitt, Roy F. -- Law (Box 16)
    - Pryor, Frederic L. -- Economics (Box 16)
    - Pulgram, Ernst -- Romance Languages (Box 16)
    - Pulver, Earl B. -- Military Science (Box 16)
    - Purdom, Thomas L. -- Bureau of Appts (Box 16)
    - Quackenbush, Mildred I. -- Nursing (Box 16)
    - Rabinowitz, Patricia W. -- Social Work (Box 16)
    - Rabinowitz, Deborah -- Ecology and Evolutionary Biology (Box 16)
    - Rabkin, Eric -- English, LSA Dean (Box 16)
    - Radock, Michael -- Public Relations (Box 16)
    - Rae, James W., Jr. -- Physical Medicine (Box 16)
    - Ramfjord, Sigurd -- Dentistry (Box 16)
    - Ramsdell, Lewis S. -- Mineralogy (Box 16)
    - Ransom, Henry K. -- Surgery (Box 16)
    - Rapoport, Anatol -- Mental Health (Box 16)
    - Rasmussen, Glen R. -- Flint, Education (Box 16)
    - Rathcke, Beverly J. -- Biology (?) (Box 16)
    - Rea, Walter B. -- Dean of Men (Box 16)
    - Reade, Maxwell O. -- Math (Box 16)
    - Reebel, Katherine R. -- Social Work (Box 16)
    - Reed, John W. -- Law (Box 16)
    - Reichart, Walter A. -- German (Box 16)
    - Reichenbach, Karl H. -- History (Box 16)
    - Reider, David H. -- Design (Box 16)
    - Reidy, John -- English (Box 16)
    - Reimann, Irvin G. -- Exhibit Museum, Zoo (Box 16)
    - Remer, Charles F. -- Economics (Box 16)
    - Remington, Richard -- Public Health (Box 16)
    - Revelli, William D. -- Wind Instruments (Box 16)
    - Rewoldt, Stewart H. -- Marketing (Box 16)
    - Rice, Warner G. -- English (Box 17)
    - Richards, Albert G. -- Dentistry (Box 17)
    - Ridenour, Gerald M. -- Public Health (Box 17)
    - Riegel, John W. -- Industrial Relations (Box 17)
    - Riley, Gardner M. -- Obstetrics (Box 17)
    - Rinehart, Constance -- Library Science (Box 17)
    - Rizki, Tahir M. -- Biology (Box 17)
    - Robbins, Frank E. -- University Press (Box 17)
    - Robinson, William D. -- Internal Medicine (Box 17)
    - Robinson, William G. -- Biological Chemistry (Box 17)
    - Roeber, Edward C. -- Education (Box 17)
    - Rogers, James Speed -- Zoology (Box 17)
    - Rondell, Paul A. -- Physiology (Box 17)
    - Rosen, Sidney -- Group Dynamics (Box 17)
    - Rosenberg, Jakob -- Fine Arts (Box 17)
    - Ross, Gilbert -- Violin (Box 17)
    - Rosseelo, Gustave O. -- Violin (Box 17)
    - Roth, Walter M. -- Plant (Box 17)
    - Rothe, Erich H. -- Math (Box 17)
    - Rowe, Kenneth T. -- English (Box 17)
    - Rowe, Tom D. -- Dean of Pharmacy (Box 17)
    - Rugen, Mabel E. -- Health Education (Box 17)
    - Ryder, Meyer S. -- Industrial Relations (Box 17)
    - Sahlins, Marshall D. -- Anthropology (Box 17)
    - Salmon, James Daniel -- Music (Box 17)
    - Samuelson, Hans -- Math (Box 17)
    - Sandalow, Terrance -- Dean of Law School (Box 17)
    - Sandor, Gyorgy -- Piano (Box 17)
    - Sands, Richard H. -- Physics (Box 17)
    - Sawyer, Charles -- Museum (Box 17)
    - Sawyer, Ralph -- Dean of Grad. School Physics (Box 17)
    - Sawyer, Thomas M., Jr. -- English (Box 17)
    - Sayles, Leonard -- Industrial Relations (Box 17)
    - Schaadt, Leonard -- Business Manager (Box 17)
    - Schafer, Robert G. -- History (Box 17)
    - Scharenberg, Konstantin -- Psychiatry (Box 17)
    - Schetzer, Julius D. -- Aeronautical Eng (Box 17)
    - Schlatter, William J. -- Accounting (Box 17)
    - Schmale, Herbert T. -- Psychiatry (Box 17)
    - Schmidt, Leo A. -- Accounting (Box 17)
    - Schneidewind, Richard -- Metallurgical Eng (Box 17)
    - Schorger, William D. -- Anthropology (Box 17)
    - Schoch, Henry K. -- Internal Medicine (Box 17)
    - Schoepfle, Chester S. -- Chemistry (Box 17)
    - Schroeder, Dorothy -- Social Work (Box 17)
    - Schull, William J. -- Zoology (Box 17)
    - Schumacher, Hazen -- Television (Box 17)
    - Schwartz, Frank L. -- Mechanical Eng (Box 17)
    - Scott, James D. -- Advertising (Box 17)
    - Scott, Norman R. -- Dearborn Campus Dean (Box 17)
    - Scott, Raymond C. -- Engineering (Box 17)
    - Sears, Richard L. -- Drawing (Box 17)
    - Seashore, Stanley E. -- Social Research (Box 17)
    - Seager, Allan -- English (Box 17)
    - Sedlander, Norman R. -- Engineering (Box 17)
    - Segal, Stanley J. -- Psychology (Box 17)
    - Seidler, Ingo -- German (Box 17)
    - Sellars, Roy W. -- Philosophy (Box 17)
    - Selzer, Melvin L. -- Medical School (Box 17)
    - Senseman, Wilfred M. -- English (Box 17)
    - Service, Elman R. -- Anthropology (Box 17)
    - Sevcenko, Ihor -- Slavic Languages (Box 17)
    - Shaffer, Robert L. -- Botany (Box 17)
    - Shappiro, David G. -- Biology (Box 17)
    - Sharp, Harry P. -- Sociology (Box 17)
    - Shartel, Burke -- Law (Box 17)
    - Shaw, Wilfred B. -- Alumni Relations (Box 17)
    - Sheldon, John M. -- Internal Medicine (Box 17)
    - Shepard, John F. -- Psychology (Box 17)
    - Sherlock, Robert H. -- Civil Engineering (Box 17)
    - Shigley, Joseph E. -- Mechanical Eng (Box 17)
    - Shillito, Frederick H. -- Medicine (Box 17)
    - Shohara, Hide -- Japanese (Box 17)
    - Shortt, James D., Jr. -- University Relations (Box 17)
    - Sichel, Martin -- Aeronautical Eng (Box 17)
    - Siebert, Clarence A. -- Chem. & Met. Eng (Box 17)
    - Siegel, Keeve Milton -- Electrical Eng., Radiation Lab (Box 17)
    - Sill, Charles H. -- Real Estate (Box 17)
    - Simes, Lewis M. -- Law (Box 17)
    - Simons, Charles S. -- Physics (Box 17)
    - Sinai, Nathan -- Public Health (Box 17)
    - Singer, J. David -- Political Science (Box 17)
    - Sink, Charles A. -- Univ. Musical Soc (Box 17)
    - Sinnott, Maurice J. -- Chem. & Met. Eng (Box 17)
    - Skolimowski, Henryk -- Humanities (Box 17)
    - Slawson, Chester B. -- Mineralogy (Box 17)
    - Slezak, Edward J. -- Physical Education (Box 17)
    - Sliepoevich, Cedomir M. -- Chem. & Met. Eng (Box 17)
    - Sloan, Herbert E., Jr. -- Surgery (Box 17)
    - Slobodkin, Lawrence B. -- Zoology (Box 17)
    - Slosson, Preston -- History (Box 17)
    - Smeaton, William G. -- Chemistry (Box 17)
    - Smillie, John W. -- Ophthalmology (Box 17)
    - Smith, Alexander H. -- Botany (Box 17)
    - Smith, Donald E. P. -- Reading Improvement (Box 17)
    - Smith, Frederick E. -- Zoologist (Box 17)
    - Smith, Gerald R. -- Ecology, Evolutionary Biology (Box 17)
    - Smith, Glenn P. -- Trombone (Box 17)
    - Smith, Shirley W. -- Vice President (Box 17)
    - Smith, Wray -- Administrator (Box 17)
    - Snortum, Niel K. -- English (Box 17)
    - Snyder, Richard -- Highway Safety Research Institute (Box 17)
    - Snyder, Walter F. -- Public Health (Box 17)
    - Sollenberger, Arlene -- Voice (Box 17)
    - Sonsmith, Henry A. -- Vocational Education (Box 17)
    - Soop, Everett J. -- UM Extension (Box 17)
    - Sorenson, Allan R. -- Regent (Box 17)
    - Souza, Laurence E. -- Nursing (Box 17)
    - Sparrow, Frederick K. -- Botany (Box 17)
    - Spaulding, Albert C. -- Archaeology (Box 17)
    - Spencer, Nelson W. -- Electrical Eng (Box 17)
    - Spivey, W. Allen -- Statistics (Box 17)
    - Spuhler, James N. -- Anthropology (Box 17)
    - Spurlin, Paul M. -- French (Box 17)
    - Stager, Augustus -- Swimming Coach (Box 17)
    - Stahly, Mary S. -- Psychiatry (Box 17)
    - Stasheff, Edward -- Speech (Box 17)
    - Stason, E. Blythe -- Law (Box 17)
    - Staubach, Charles Neff -- Spanish (Box 17)
    - Steffek, Ralph L. -- Extension Centers (Box 17)
    - Steigerwalt, Albert K. -- Business History (Box 17)
    - Stein, Eric -- Law (Box 17)
    - Steiner, Eric E. -- Botany (Box 17)
    - Steinhoff, William R. -- English (Box 17)
    - Stevens, Albert K. -- English (Box 17)
    - Stevens, Walter -- Safety (Box 17)
    - Stevenson, Charles L. -- Philosophy (Box 17)
    - Stevenson, Fred G. -- UM Extension (Box 17)
    - Stevenson, Russell A. -- Business Admin (Box 17)
    - Stewart, David H. -- English (Box 17)
    - Stewart, Kenneth N. -- Journalism (Box 17)
    - Stewart, R. C. -- Libraries (Box 17)
    - Stillings, Frank S. -- Music (Box 17)
    - Stockard, Alfred H. -- Zoology (Box 17)
    - Stockton, Eric W. -- English (Box 17)
    - Stokes, Donald F. -- Political Science (Box 17)
    - Stolper, Wolfgang F. -- Economics (Box 17)
    - Stone, Kenneth A. -- Electrical Eng (Box 17)
    - Storer, Robert W. -- Zoology (Box 17)
    - Stowe, Leland -- Journalism (Box 17)
    - Streeten, David H. P. -- Internal Medicine (Box 17)
    - Streeten, Victor L. -- Hydraulics (Box 17)
    - Stroke, George -- Electrical Eng (Box 17)
    - Stubbins, William H. -- Band (Box 17)
    - Stubbs, Harry E. -- Engineering Research (Box 17)
    - Stumm, Erwin C. -- Geology (Box 17)
    - Sturgis, Cyrus C. -- Internal Medicine (Box 17)
    - Summer, Elizabeth -- Religious Affairs (Box 17)
    - Super, Robert Henry -- English (Box 17)
    - Sussman, Alfred S. -- Rackham Dean, Botany (Box 17)
    - Sutherland, Gordon A. -- Music (Box 17)
    - Sweet, Waldo E. -- Latin (Box 17)
    - Swinton, Roy S. -- Engineering Mech (Box 17)
    - Swniton, Stan -- Michigan Daily (Box 17)
    - Swinyard, Alfred -- Business Admin., Bur. of Bus. Rsrch (Box 17)
  - T-Z
    - Taggart, Herbert F. -- Accounting (Box 17)
    - Tamres, Milton -- Chemistry (Box 17)
    - Tannenbaum, Arnold S. -- Survey Research Ctr (Box 17)
    - Taylor, James H. -- Industrial Relations (Box 17)
    - Taylor, Mary N. -- Social Work (Box 17)
    - Taylor, Robert C. -- Chemistry (Box 17)